Hamid Safdari

Developer

Java Script | React | Node js | Python | PHP |

About Me

As a developer, I am driven by the desire to create innovative solutions that make a difference in people's lives. I believe that technology has the power to transform the world, and I want to be a part of that transformation.

Every new code I make is due to my passion for programming, and this passion makes the challenges and difficulties on my way easy. So, I love experiencing new challenges and always try to push myself to face them. With this approach, I always learn new things and programming never becomes monotonous for me. If your mindset is similar to mine, I would be happy to walk the path together and gain new experiences.

Highlights Of Qualifications

- Talented Developer with extensive experience in JavaScript, Python and PHP; Good knowledge of SQL and NoSQL Databases
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Strong organizational and problem-solving skills with great attention to detail
- Proven ability to learn quickly; willing to learn new technologies and skills

EXPERIENCES

Front-end Developer

12/2023 - 10/2024 (10 months)

Charter118 🖸

- Collaborated with other 3 team members to produce a web app which users can reserve flight tickets, hotel reservation and tour packages
- designed and developed a full feature panel for admin and users

Full-stack Developer

2020 - 2023 (3 years)

Freelance

- Collaborated lots of projects in front and back-end
- Developed many projects from scratch like "RealEstate", "Jobify" and etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree — *Computer Engineering* 2018 - 2023

Bahar Institute of Higher Education

Phone:

0939-495-7726

E-Mail:

i.hamidsafdari@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://hamidsafdari.onrender.com/

LinkedIn :

www.linkedin.com/in/hamid-safdari-08895a290

Github:

https://github.com/HamidSafdari7

Languages:

Persian

Mother tongue

English

Advanced and fluent in all skills (Speaking - Listening - Reading - Writing)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

- Java Script Type Script
- PHP
- Python

Web Technologies

- HTML
- CSS
- React js
- Next js
- Node Js
- Express Js
- Laravel
- Tailwind Css
- Github

Databases

- MongoDB
- PostgreSql
- MySql

WEB PROJECTS

#1 — My Portfolio

View Demo

Technologies used:

HTML - CSS - Java Script - Bootstrap - Git

About Project:

- This is my personal website, where I put my Resume and Projects I've done
- I highly recommend you to check it out, so you can see my abilities in web developing

#2 — *Jobify*

<u>View Demo</u> <u>View Src Code</u>

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - Material UI - UseReducer - UseContext - Styled Component

Back: Node Js - Express Js **DataBase**: MongoDB

About Project:

- Successfully built a responsive website for an imaginary Job Seeking Platform
- You can add your jobs as an "Employer" or You can find your dream job as an "Employee"

#3 — RealEstate

<u>View Demo</u> <u>View Src Code</u>

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - Jquery -

Bootstrap

Back: PHP - Laravel 10

DataBase: MYSQL

About Project:

- In this website you can buy or sell or even rent properties and houses
- it has an "Admin Panel" which you can control everything on this website(like: add agents and edit them, change the accessibility of each agent, add or delete properties and lots of other things you can imagin...)
- It has a "Real Time Chat" which users can chat dynamically with agents.

#4 — Charter 118

charter118.ir

Technologies used:

Front: React

Back : Laravel - PHP

DataBase : MYSQL

About Project:

- A web app for reserving flight tickets, hotel, tour packages and etc
- supported languages like English and Arabic
- user-friendly and simple to use
- full online reservation

#5 — Smart Brain

View Demo View Src Code

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React

Back : Node Js - Express Js

DataBase : PostgreSql

About Project:

- A Website where you can put your images and only by one click it will recognize the faces in the image
- Fully responsive and user-friendly

#6 — News Aggregator Website

View Src code

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - MUI - UseReducer - UseContext - Styled Component

Back : Laravel

DataBase : MYSQL

About Project:

- A Fully responsive website
- I developed both front and backend
- front = React
- Back = Laravel
- Gathered many sources like BBC, CNN and etc
- Using NewsAPI